Mohit Kumar

github.com/moh-hit linkedin.com/in/moh-it10 moh.hit1012@gmail.com

Bangalore

+91 8197920517

Love to code, design, build.

Hey there! I'm a Software Developer who loves UI design and creating awesome web and mobile apps. With solid experience in major frameworks and tech, I build user-friendly and engaging experiences. Let's create something amazing together!

Work experience

Fijit

Senior Software Developer

June 2023 - Current

React Native, Native Code, Nest.js, Next.js, React.js

- Building and managing company's app (<u>Play store</u> / <u>App store</u> as <u>Fijit</u>)
- Created the latest version of their app from scratch and managing features for the product. Integration on Unity games within the app through webgl and webview bridging

Streak

Senior Software Developer

March 2021 - June 2023

React.js, React Native, Next.js, Golang, Mongo, Redis, Wordpress

- Developed and managed multiple web apps, <u>streak.tech</u>, <u>academy.streak.tech</u>, <u>technicals.zerodha.com</u>
- Managed product and feature development of their primary mobile app (Streak)

Propstory

Frontend Developer Intern

January 2020 - August 2020

Javascript, React.js

- Developed a web application which lets you edit any html page and lets you integrate various tracking pixels into it without any code knowledge for the company.
- Managed all sorts of landing pages and sites for major real estates companies.

Skills

- → React Native, Expo
- → React.js / Next.js, Typescript
- → Golang / Node.js

Tools

- → Version control : Git
- → DB: Redis, Mongo
- → Sentry, Firebase

Education

East Point College Of Engg & Tech

Kendriya Vidyalaya ASC Centre

BTech. in CSE

2016 - 2020

10th - 12th Standard

2014 - 2016